Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Awards
  - Holland Tulip Festival Band Review; William Moffit Adjudicator, 1967 (Ovs box 52, Item 2)
  - Marquis Who's Who Publications Board; Who's Who America; 44th Edition, 1986-1987 (Ovs box 52, Item 3)
  - Marquis Who's Who Publications Board; Who's Who America; 44th Edition, 1986-1987 (Ovs box 52, Item 4)
  - Marquis Who's Who Publications Board; Who's Who America; 45th Edition, 1988-1989 (Ovs box 52, Item 5)
  - Marquis Who's Who Publications Board; Who's Who America; 46th Edition, 1990-1991 (Ovs box 52, Item 6)
  - Sandy Lake Amusement Park; Band Fun-Fest, 1973-1982 (Ovs box 52, Item 7)
  - Texas Bandmasters Association; 50th Anniversary Convention (Ovs box 52, Item 8)
  - University of Arizona; Milton B. Nunamaker Distinguished Director's Award, 1976 (Ovs box 52, Item 9)
  - UH Student's Association Senate, January 17, 1977 (Ovs box 52, Item 10)
  - Boyertown Texas Preview; Guest Conductor, 1971 (Ovs box 53, Item 1)
  - Defiance Marching Band Spectacular, 1978 (Ovs box 54, Item 1)
  - Hockey Team/Hockey Band, 1967 (Ovs box 54, Item 2)
  - Penholder (Ovs box 54, Item 3)
  - Cougar Marching Band; Lefest, Merle and Deb, 1980-1981 (Ovs box 55, Item 1)
  - Hoover High School, May 14, 1980 (Ovs box 55, Item 2)
  - Miscellaneous Award (Ovs box 55, Item 3)
  - Baldwin Wallace Conservatory, 1950 (Ovs box 56, Item 1)
  - Freedom Foundation at Valley Forge, 1977 (Ovs box 56, Item 2)
  - Texas Bandmaster's Association; President, 1980 (Ovs box 56, Item 3)
  - Chair's Award; Houston Alumni Organization, September 20, 2007 (Ovs box 57, Item 1)
  - College Football Centennial Award, 1969 (Ovs box 58, Item 1)
    OVS Box 58 (formerly Box 42) and contents missing as of March 25, 2015.
  - Indiana Office of Governor Otis R. Bowen, 1977 (Ovs box 58, Item 2)
  - New Philadelphia; "Bill Moffit Day", April 6, 1973 (Ovs box 58, Item 3)
  - Ohio House of Representatives; Representative Alan E. Norris, undated (Ovs box 58, Item 4)
  - Otterbien College, 1973 (Ovs box 58, Item 5)
  - Otterbien College, 1975 (Ovs box 58, Item 6)
- Jacksonville Community Band Materials
  This series consists of materials used by William C. Moffit in his role as founder of the Jacksonville Community Band. Materials include scores, manuscript parts, and published arrangements used by the Jacksonville Community Band. Additional research material can be found in Series 3. Additional manuscript parts can be found in Series 6. Additional published arrangements by William Moffit can be found in Series 9. Additional published music books can be found in Series 15. This series contains 59 folders and original folder and item order has be maintained whenever possible. Oversize materials can be found in OVS Box 60.
  - "State Song of Florida" Composed by Stephen Collins Foster and arranged by Bill Moffit (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - "At the Bullfight with Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass" (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - "The Wide Wide World of Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass" (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - "Sheet Music Full Arrangements Music Envelopes Full Scores" (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "Flagler College, Hail to Thee, Alma Mater" (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "Showcase for Band" (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - "Bowler-Birthday Fanfare" (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - "Birthday Present" (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "Soundpower 'Patterns for Percussion'" (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - "Band Taps" (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "Son of a Preacher Man" (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - "Wedding March" (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - "'Hi-tech' for Marching Band" (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - "Victory March, Notre Dame Victory March, Brass and Percussion Score" (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - "Victory March, Notre Dame Victory March, Woodwinds Score" (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - "Rocket America" (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - "God Bless America" (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - "Hail to Thee, New Philadephia" (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - "American Prelude" (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - "Jolly Old St. Nicholas" (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "Bugler's Dream" (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - "Strike Up The Band" (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - "March America" (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - "Evil Woman Don't Play Your Games With Me" (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - "Two Brass Fanfares, Cotton Bowl Fanfare & Fanfare on Funiculi Funicula" (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - "Three Funky Cadences" (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - "Dixie Cadence" (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - "The Christmas Song (Chestnuts Roasting On An Open Fire)" (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - "Cole Porter, A Symphonic Portrait for Concert Band" (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - "Tequila" (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - "Hail Purdue" (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - "Louie, Louie" (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - "God Bless the U.S.A." (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - "Arminda" (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - "Alleluia, from "Exultate, Jubilate" Motet" (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - "Tenderly" (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - "Big Band Dixie" (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - "First Suite in E♭ For Military Band (1909)" (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - "God Bless America" (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - "Irving Berlin, Five Star Tunes with Piano Accompaniment, Always, Marie, Blue Skies, Alexander's Ragtime Band, and What'll I Do" (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - "Itsy Bitsy Teeny Weeny Yellow Polkadot Bikini" (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - "Christmas in Song" (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - "Florida Bandmasters Association, Inc." (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - "Music Education Solutions" (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Emailed article about International Copyrights from Mark Eustler (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - "March Graustark by C. Linder" (Ovs box 60, Folder 1)
  - "A Song of India (Piano Solo) by Nikolas Rimsky-Korsakov" (Ovs box 60, Folder 2)
  - "Cowboy Yodel words and music by Gene Autry" (Ovs box 60, Folder 3)
  - "Musical Memories for Pianoforte by Paul Ducelle" (Ovs box 60, Folder 4)
  - "Twentieth Century March and Two-Step by J. Messina" (Ovs box 60, Folder 5)
  - "The Popular Songs Monthly" (Ovs box 60, Folder 6)
  - "Popular Dance Music for the Piano" (Ovs box 60, Folder 7)
  - "Famous Marches Arranged for the Piano" (Ovs box 60, Folder 8)
  - "Simple Simon March Two-Step by Wm. Murray Simpson" (Ovs box 60, Folder 9)
  - "Beautiful Ohio Waltz by Mary Earl" (Ovs box 60, Folder 10)
  - "The Dublin Rag, The Character Song Hit in Frazee & Lederer's French Vaudeville Madame Sherry" (Ovs box 60, Folder 11)
  - "Birthday Present, a Bill Moffit Manuscript Arrangement" (Ovs box 60, Folder 12)
  - "American Prelude" (Ovs box 60, Folder 13)
  - "Tenderly" (Ovs box 60, Folder 14)
- Pamphlets and Programs
  This series consists of pamphlets and programs William C. Moffit mainly gathered from various conferences and band events, as well as promotional materials he received featuring him or his bands. This series contains 99 folders and original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible.
  - "Arlington House, The Robert E. Lee Memorial" pamphlet (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - "Public Services in the Library of Congress, Locations and Hours of Opening" pamphlet (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - "Service to the Nation, The Library of Congress" (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - "Fanfare", Spring 1987 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - "CIDA, Christian Instrumental Directors Association, Newsletter", May 1987 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - "Pomp and Circumstance (Theme) Band Spectacular, Elgar-Waters" (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - "Joint Concert" (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - "American Bandmasters' Association Annual, 1932" (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - "Akron Public Schools Music May Festival" (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - "Bandorama '84, Around the World with the Purdue Bands" (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - "Big Ten Band Directors Directory Update", 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 56)
  - "All American Marching Band" (Box 50, Folder 57)
  - "Trip Itinerary - Purdue vs. O.S.U. and Marion Show" (Box 50, Folder 58)
  - "Purdue University Presents, Purdue University - Northwestern University Football Game", November 2, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 59)
  - "Instrumental Directors Guide", 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 60)
  - "Welcome to the Purdue University Bands and Symphony Orchestra" (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - "Bandinage Presents the Lone Arranger, Volume 27.1" (Box 50, Folder 62)
  - "Purdue University "All-American" Marching Band, Purdue vs. Notre Dame", September 10, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 63)
  - "National/International Music Festivals, Inc." (Box 50, Folder 64)
  - "Purdue University Bands, Purdue - University of Notre Dame Football Game", September 10, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 65)
  - "Fanfare", Fall 1984 (Box 50, Folder 66)
  - "University of Houston Cougar Marching Band", January 30, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 67)
  - "Hal Leonard Presents The Sound of America" (Box 50, Folder 68)
  - "The Purdue Alumnus", November 1981 (Box 50, Folder 69)
  - "Bandorama Script", 1983 (Box 50, Folder 70)
  - "Purdue University News", October 8-10, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 71)
  - "Purdue University "All-American" Marching Band", September 15-November 3, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 72)
  - "Purdue University "All-American" Marching Band", October 19-November 2, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 73)
  - "Dan Ryder 1988 Marching Band Catalog" (Box 50, Folder 74)
  - "The Mississippi Rag" (Box 50, Folder 75)
  - "Fanfare", Fall 1986 (Box 50, Folder 76)
  - "University of Houston, Central Campus, We're the 1s" (Box 50, Folder 77)
  - "The Purdue University "All-American" Marching Band 29th Annual Awards Banquet", November 24, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 78)
  - “McCutcheon Maverick Bands 1983 Spring Awards Concert Featuring Concert Band, Symphonic Band, and Jazz Band” (Box 50, Folder 79)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa Certificate (Box 50, Folder 80)
  - Lafayette Citizens Band, 1987 Summer Concert Series (Box 50, Folder 81)
  - “37th Annual National Awards, Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge", 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 82)
  - “Just For You… Our Customer… The Most Beautiful New Record and Tape Treasures We’ve Ever Offered You!” (Box 50, Folder 83)
  - “Busy Bee Band & Honeybees Seventeenth Annual Performance", March 20-22, and April 1-5, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 84)
  - “The Purdue University “All-American” Marching band 26th Annual Banquet Awards", November 21, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 85)
  - "The Band Directory", 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 86)
  - “Announcing the Annual National Awards, Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge” (Box 50, Folder 87)
  - “Nicsinger Uniform Co., Inc.” (Box 50, Folder 88)
  - “Texas Bandmasters’ Association, 34th Annual, New Music – Marching band Clinic", July 26-29, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 89)
  - “Triad, Queen City Conference", December 1981-January 1982 (Box 50, Folder 90)
  - "35th Annual Med-West National Band and Orchestra Clinic", December 15-19, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - “The Department of Bands at Purdue University Present Bandorama ’84, Around the World With The Purdue Bands", October 6, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - “American Bandmasters Association 49th Annual Convention Kansas City", March 1-6, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - “Band Media Guide, The “All-American” Marching Band", 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - “Tuscarawas County, Ohio” (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - “The Purdue Alumnus, The ’Jazz Age’ at Purdue, then and now", November 1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - “The American Bandmasters Association, Directory", 1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - “The Tuscarawas Valley, In the Heart of Ohio” (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - “The National Band Association Hall of Fame of Distinguished Band Directors” (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - “Schoenbrunn, The Romantic Story of Ohio’s First Town” (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - “Purdue University Jazz Band, Mid-West International Band And Orchestra Clinic", December 17, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - “The Sixth Annual Buckeye Invitational Marching Band Festival", October 8, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - “Texas Bandmasters Association, 39th Annual Convention", July 27-30, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - “ABA Band Presents, The Greatest Blow on Earth, ‘A Tribute to Merle Evans'", March 2-5, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - “Band Media Guide, The “All-American” Marching Band", 1983-1984 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - “Who’s Who in the South and the Southwest, Fifteenth Edition", 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - “Hotel Osaka Grand” (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - “37th Annual Montgomery County Music Festival", March 11, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - “1982 Kansas Beef Cook-off Recipes” (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - “University of Houston “Cougar” Marching Band", 1970 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - “Alabama State College Marching Hornets Presents Bill Moffit, Patterns in Motion", May 3, 4, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - “Hal Leonard Presents the Sound of America, Highlights from our Catalog”, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - “The Purdue Alumnus", March 1988 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - “Joint Concert” (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - “Moffit Yen Year Club Members” (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - “Who’s Who in America, 44th Edition” (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - “The Care and Feeding of the Band Musician” (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - “University of Houston Show Book", October 2, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - “How to Stage Bill Moffit’s “That’s Entertaining” Features” (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - “Bill Moffit’s Soundpower, Marching Band Clinic Materials, University of Houston” (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - “Concert Filled with Happy Songs” (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - “Big Ten Band Directors Directory Update” (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - “Moffit “Showpower” Titles, Entertainment Features for Every Band, Performance Suggestions” (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - “Illinois vs. Purdue Boilermaker”, October 22, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - “The Fourteenth Annual Ohio Band Directors Conference", December 7, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - “Purdue Reports", September 1981 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Publicity Release - Dr. Willam C. Moffit (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - “Office of the Mayor Ronald L. Malone of Marion, Ohio Proclamation", October 18, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - “Certificate of Recognition from The Grand Opening of Purdue University’s Visitor Information Center", 1986 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - “ABA Band Award of Demerit” (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - “A Journalistic Interview with Dr. William C. Moffit", Feburary 19, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - “Bandinage", October 18, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - “Arranging Happiness”, Laura Reasoner, Instrumentalist Magazine (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - “The Number one Marching Band in the Land” (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - “Purdue University “All-American” Marching Band, Highlights of 1983” (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - “Purdue University “All-American” Marching Band”, September 21, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - “Strike Up the Band! Purdue’s All-American Marching Band” (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Eva-Tone Soundsheets, Inc. (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - “Kennedy Space Center, Florida, Visitor’s Guide” (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - “Why it pays to be an ASCAP Member” (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - “Purdue 1985 Football Media Guide” (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - “Band Media Guide, The “All-American” Marching Band", 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - “Selected Christmas Music for Concert and Marching Bands, Full and String Orchestras and Ensembles” (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - “Freedom Foundation at Valley Forge, The Annual National Awards", 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 54)
- Newspaper Articles
  This series consists of newspaper articles featuring William C. Moffit or his bands. This series contains 73 folders and orginal folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible.
  - “P.D.Q. Bach, His biggest fan actually discovered him, his works” (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Crawfordsville Journal and Review, Leisuretime, “30 Years later", October 19, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - “Des Moines Register", October 16, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Purdue University Perspective, “Bill Moffit’s joy of music” (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Purdue Exponent, Vol. 101, No. 165, “World’s Largest Drum?”, November 25, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Kenton Times, “Moffit records KHS fight song", October 12, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - The Marion Star, “Special Musical Treat", October 19, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Journal and Courier, “Home Advantage drummed up by the leader of the band”, February 29, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Lansing State Journal, Metro, “Purdue Band gives Falcone home concert", September 30, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Journal and Courier, “Thanks for caring", September 24, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - “Bang the drum slowly…,” “Overture Finale,” and “Reflecting on his role in the race” (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Wander Loste Minstrel, Vol. 5, No. 1 “Purdue Band celebrates 100 year of firsts", January 23, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Journal and Courier, “Boo, J&C, boo, Boilers; yeah, Band!”, September 19, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Journal and Courier, “Marching band bill on last leg", February 18, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Journal and Courier, “Letters: ‘Personality cult’ hits River City", December 2, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - “Community History", February 15, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - “Boilermaker band in Japan", November 5, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - “Purdue Musicians leave for Japan", November 1, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - “Spanky” comic by Mike Mitchell (Box 51, Folder 73)
  - Indianapolis Star, “Band drum, in parade and Garfield’s pal”, May 29, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - News clippings, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - “Never an off day for Purdue’s band” (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - “Band of Renown” (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - “What’s new at Purdue” (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - “Dr. Frank Clifford” (Box 51, Folder 79)
  - The Purdue Exponent, “Bandorama ’87", September 21, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - The Columbus Dispatch, “Purdue band’s flash clashes with OSU’s marching style", October 20, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 81)
  - “Musing with the Moffits” (Box 51, Folder 82)
  - Chicago Tribune, “The Golden Girl” (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - “’Sloopy’ hangs in there for top song” (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - “Essential Musical Terms” (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Newsweek, “The Magnificent Ten", November 11, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 86)
  - Chicago Tribune, “Are we joking? “A frayed knot!” These puns are the year’s best” (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - “Tar Heels, Big ten tops” (Box 51, Folder 88)
  - Journal and Courier, “Purdue band’s history commemorated", December 7, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 89)
  - “Go on backing Purdue Bands” (Box 51, Folder 90)
  - “Purdue fans expect loss” (Box 51, Folder 91)
  - Chicago Tribune, “A reader response to beat the band", November 10, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 92)
  - Chicago Tribune, “ At halftime: TV 1, marching bands 0", November 3, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 93)
  - “Points of Interest” (Box 51, Folder 94)
  - The Indianapolis Star, “Hail, Purdue band; happy 100 years!", October 12, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 95)
  - The Purdue Exponent, “Loco Motives", February 19, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 96)
  - The Purdue Exponent, “Editorial: Practice makes perfect", September 22, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 97)
  - The Purdue Exponent, “Bang the drum slowly…”, May 26, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 98)
  - Times West-Virginia, “Busy Bee Band & Honeybees welcomes Follies ’86 Dr. William C. Moffit", April 3, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 99)
  - Journal and Courier, “Homecoming Splash: Purdue kicks off spirited weekend", October 4, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 100)
  - Journal and Courier, “Purdue band high-steps to 100 years", October 4, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 101)
  - Journal and Courier, “Purdue band will unfurl special effects for IU", February 24, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 102)
  - Newslife, “Special Musical Treat", October 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 103)
  - Newslife, “Combined Bands won crowd", October 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 104)
  - Newslife, “Purdue, Harding bands perform", October 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 105)
  - Newslife, “Purdue’s Girl in Black", October 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 106)
  - Harding Herald, Vol. 66, No. 3, “Purdue: Moffit enjoys Harding, explains All-American Band", October 25, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 107)
  - The Purdue Exponent, Vol. 103, No. 120, “Band Celebrates Festivities noting Constitution’s b-day", September 17, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 108)
  - The Purdue Exponent, Vol. 103, No. 120, “Annual Bandorama Brings Musical Medley to Hall of Music", September 17, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 109)
  - The Purdue Exponent, Vol. 102, No. 73, “Celebrity Bash", April 30, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 110)
  - Journal Review, Crawfordsville, Indiana, “Mr. and Mrs. Eutsler", November 5, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 111)
  - Herald Journal, Monticello Indiana, “Monticello’s Golden Girl Glitters", October 9, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 112)
  - Journal and Courier, Metro B, “World’s Largest Drum needs a ride", September 22, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 113)
  - Journal and Courier, Metro B, “All fans survived the ‘cultural collision", September 17, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 114)
  - Journal and Courier, Living D, “Bandorama 81”, October 9, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 115)
  - Journal and Courier, “Striking up the 400", September 13, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 116)
  - The Mexia Daily News, “Wortham band takes ‘first chair’ award", April 21, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 117)
  - “Ta Ra Ra, Boom! Concert to feature celebrities” (Box 51, Folder 118)
  - The Daily Illini, “The Illini, lost, but Purdue just can’t win", October 15, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 119)
  - The Cynthiana Argus, “Hoosier Celebration ’88 Official Song Made Debut at Indianapolis 500", June 15, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 120)
  - Purdue Exponent, “All American, Purdue band to travel, entertain in Japan", October 18, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 121)
  - “Canadians hire Purdue Musician” (Box 51, Folder 122)
  - Journal and Courier, Local B, “Guest to conduct pops concert tonight", April 25, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 123)
  - “All American Marching Band", 1981 (Box 51, Folder 124)
  - “Purdue’s band director says he is building on tradition” (Box 51, Folder 125)
  - Journal and Courier, Metro Region B, “Bird’s-eye view of enthusiastic fans”, November 1, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 126)
  - “Music group participates in Race Day festivities", May 26, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 127)
  - “’Eat ‘em up!, eat’em up!’ Cougar band is on the march again" (Box 51, Folder 128)
  - The Houston Post, “Hogs try SWC buffet again", February 27, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 129)
  - The Daily Cougar, “The Sound and the Power of William C. Moffit", January 24, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 130)
  - The Daily Cougar, “A traffic sign on Cullen Boulevard...", November 9, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 131)
  - Houston Chronicle, “UH Cougars, Man behind the band", November 10, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 132)
  - Houston Chronicle, “UH band collecting blood in Tony’s memory", March 25, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 133)
  - San Antonio Light, "Bandmasters meet in S.A.", July 31, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 134)
  - The Florida Alligator, “Tools of the trade", August 1, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 135)
  - The Dallas Morning News, “Irish blister Coogs, 100-77", March 13, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 136)
  - The Redford Observer, “Thurston director pokes and twirls to move the band", November 4, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 137)
  - The Cougar, “Moffit quits position as UH band director", June 3, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 138)
  - The Purdue Exponent, “Band-aid aids band", October 5, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 139)
  - Journal and Courier, “Home advantage drummed up by leader of the band", February 29, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 140)
  - Journal and Courier, “ ‘Hail Purdue’ at Olympics, too", July 23, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 141)
  - The Repository, “HOF Festival is off to colorful start", July 29, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 142)
  - The Daily Texan, “Shot, kidnapped, and once radioactive, Big Bertha booms through 30 years", October 10, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 143)
  - Chicago Tribune, “The Golden Girl", October 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 144)
  - The 63rd National FFA Convention "Proceedings", “National Band", November 8-10, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 145)
  - Folio Weekly, “ Bandmaster, Northeast Florida’s very own music man", November 29, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 146)
  - The Florida Times-Union, “Sounds of the season", December 3, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 147)
  - The Florida Times-Union, “Band leaders in discord", December 9, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 148)
  - Fanfare, “Bowl trip was decidedly ‘rosy’", Spring 2001 (Box 51, Folder 149)